>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我刚才提到了一些神奇的行为
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I referenced a bit
earlier a sort of magical behavior like
访问基本值上的属性。
accessing properties on primitive values.
记住，您可以在原始字符串上访问长度，或者
Remember, you access a length
on a primitive string or
例如，在原始编号上使用某些方法。
some method on a primitive number,
for example.
那么这项工作是如何运作的呢 ?
So how does that work?
我们如何在此处访问某些字符串值的 .length ?
How is it that we access the .length
of some string value here?
此 DOM 元素值始终为字符串。
This DOM elements value
is always a string.
那么，我们如何访问该 .length?
So how do we access that .length?
这就是所谓的拳击赛
Well, it turns out that's called boxing.
这是一种隐含的胁迫形式。
It's a form of implicit coercion.
在抽象的操作中，它也不是以同样的方式被调用的。
It's not called out in the same
way in the abstract operations.
但我认为这种精神绝对是一种隐含的胁迫。
But I think it absolutely in
spirit is an implicit coercion.
说你有这个东西不是对象
It is saying you have this
thing that is not an object and
你试图用它当它是一个物体
you're trying to use it
as if it is an object.
我， JavaScript ，我会帮你做，然后把它变成一个对象。
Me, JavaScript I'm gonna be helpful and go
ahead and make it into an object for you.
唯一的其他选项将用于 JavaScript 抛出异常。
The only other option would be for the
JavaScript to throw an exception that said
您正在尝试访问原始值上的属性。
you're trying to access
a property on an primitive value.
我很高兴 JavaScript 隐含地强制了这些原语
I am actually quite happy that JavaScript
implicitly coerces these primitives
从而使我能够访问它们的属性和方法。
into their object counterpart so that I
can access properties and methods on them.
我认为这使得代码更加清晰。
I think that makes
the code much more clear.
如果我想写代码我得把一个原始对象变成一个对象
If I wanted to write code where I had to
turn a primitive into an object just to
用它我就去写 Java
use it, I'd go write Java.
我想这就是 JavaScript 中的无名英雄之一
This, I think,
is one of the unsung heroes of JavaScript,
它能做这一拳击赛它也能做得好
that it does this boxing and
it does it well.
但它是一种隐性的胁迫。
But it is an implicit coercion.
怎么了 >> 演讲者 2:
Yes?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Is that where
这种东西的概念是来自一个物体吗 ?
this notion of everything
is an object comes from?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这就是我的意思
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It is,
that's exactly what I meant when I was
在他的言谈中人们认为一切事物都是物体
talking in the intro, that people
think that everything's an object.
事实证明事物可以像物体一样
And it turns out that things
can behave as objects, but
这不可能让他们成为一个目标
that doesn't make them an object.
这不是对象。
This is not an object.
它是一个基本字符串，在您可以访问的位置具有优化
It is a primitive string that has
an optimization in it where you can access
属性，就像它是对象一样。
a property as if it was an object.
这些都是你的计划中发生的胁迫的例子。
So these are all examples of coercion
that are happening in your programs.
我想说的更重要的一点是我们称之为胁迫还是
And the larger point that I want to
make is whether we call them coercion or
我们称它们为每一种语言的转换
we call them conversion every single
language in existence that you've ever
编程方式必须处理类型转换。
programmed in has to deal
with type conversions.
建议你写的完全是胡说八道
It is complete nonsense to
suggest that you can write
有效的合理 JavaScript 程序，无需处理类型转换。
valid reasonable JavaScript programs and
not need to deal with type conversion.
你总是会有一个字符串作为一个数字
You're always gonna have a string
that you need to treat as a number or
需要作为布尔值处理的数字。
a number that you need
to treat as a Boolean.
你必须要处理转换的问题，也就是强迫。
You are going to have to deal
with conversions, aka coercion.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这是绝对必要的，所以
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It's
absolutely necessary, so,
你会用它不管你是否承认
you're gonna use it whether
you're admitting it or not.
你真没选择
Cuz you really have no choice.